[{"answer": "More than you", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I was bored", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't know what that means", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Do you want me to make something up or paraphrase what I did the first time", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " So... why do you have to film everything", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Why do you like to film me crying", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Do you hate your parents", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " What's to understand", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "When you don't have any friends, don't play sports, don't go out, have no one talk to, nowhere to go, no one to listen to you, or no one to help you figure things out, you sort of have to figure things out by yourself. And without any of those things I have nothing but time to think about stuff", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You are so beautiful", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " You think I'm pretty", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " No one has ever told me that", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " How could you say that? I only way a hundred and ten pounds", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I am not FLAT", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " I wear a full B cup", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I am not going to take them out! You take yours out", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "We can?    Where is it", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I swear on the bond", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Not even death. I swear. Nothing will come between us, ever", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I my friend..", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Do hereby solemnly swear..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Do hereby solemnly swear..", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That I will never ask, request, or even insinuate to my friend to cease filming, no matter the situation", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "  I'm filming", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " It's on infr", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " It's dark.     You can't see anything", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " No, I don't wanna see", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What?    I'm not in the mood", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Okay, where are we gonna go", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "  Don't have to be in the mood. Doesn't matter. The camera's on, it's on.  You wanna know where we're gonna go", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " We're going to my friend to visit my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " No", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "He's suppose to be cool", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You wanted to ask me something", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You know I do", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " Do you love me", "docId": "Jimmy-and-Judy.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " I do", "qsentId": 38}]